<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<SmellBaseline>
  <ManuallySuppressedIssues></ManuallySuppressedIssues>
  <CurrentIssues>
    <ID>LongParameterList:BaseShow.kt$BaseShow$( val show: Show?, val seasons: List&lt;BaseSeason&gt;?, @Json(name = "last_collected_at") val lastCollectedAt: ZonedDateTime?, @Json(name = "listed_at") val listedAt: ZonedDateTime?, val plays: Int?, @Json(name = "last_watched_at") val lastWatchedAt: ZonedDateTime?, val aired: Int?, val completed: Int?, @Json(name = "hidden_seasons") val hiddenSeasons: List&lt;Season&gt;?, @Json(name = "next_episode") val nextEpisode: Episode? )</ID>
    <ID>LongParameterList:Comment.kt$Comment$( val id: Int?, @Json(name = "parent_id") val parentId: Int?, @Json(name = "created_at") val createdAt: ZonedDateTime?, val comment: String, val spoiler: Boolean?, val review: Boolean?, val replies: Int?, val user: User?, val movie: Movie, val show: Show, val episode: Episode )</ID>
    <ID>LongParameterList:Crew.kt$Crew$( val writing: List&lt;CrewMember&gt;?, val production: List&lt;CrewMember&gt;?, val directing: List&lt;CrewMember&gt;?, @Json(name = "costume &amp; make-up") var costumeAndMakeUp: List&lt;CrewMember&gt;?, val art: List&lt;CrewMember&gt;?, val sound: List&lt;CrewMember&gt;?, val camera: List&lt;CrewMember&gt;? )</ID>
    <ID>LongParameterList:Episode.kt$Episode$( val title: String?, val overview: String?, val rating: Double?, val votes: Int?, @Json(name = "updated_at") val updatedAt: ZonedDateTime?, @Json(name = "available_translations") val availableTranslations: List&lt;String&gt;?, val season: Int?, val number: Int?, val ids: EpisodeIds?, @Json(name = "number_abs") val numberAbs: Int?, @Json(name = "first_aired") val firstAired: ZonedDateTime? )</ID>
    <ID>LongParameterList:Movie.kt$Movie$( val year: Int?, val ids: MovieIds?, val certification: String?, val tagline: String?, val released: LocalDate?, val runtime: Int?, val trailer: String?, val homepage: String?, val language: String?, val genres: List&lt;String&gt;? )</ID>
    <ID>LongParameterList:Person.kt$Person$( val name: String?, val ids: PersonIds?, // extended info val biography: String?, val birthday: LocalDate?, val death: LocalDate?, val birthplace: String?, val homepage: String? )</ID>
    <ID>LongParameterList:Season.kt$Season$( val number: Int?, val ids: SeasonIds?, val overview: String?, val rating: Double?, val votes: Int?, @Json(name = "episode_count") val episodeCount: Int?, @Json(name = "aired_episodes") val airedEpisodes: Int?, val episodes: List&lt;Episode&gt;? )</ID>
    <ID>LongParameterList:Show.kt$Show$( val title: String?, val overview: String?, val rating: Double?, val votes: Int?, @Json(name = "updated_at") val updatedAt: ZonedDateTime?, @Json(name = "available_translations") val availableTranslations: List&lt;String&gt;?, val year: Int?, val ids: ShowIds?, @Json(name = "first_aired") val firstAired: ZonedDateTime?, val airs: Airs?, val runtime: Int?, val certification: String?, val network: String?, val country: String?, val trailer: String?, val homepage: String?, val status: Status?, val language: String?, val genres: List&lt;String&gt;? )</ID>
    <ID>LongParameterList:Stats.kt$Stats$( val watchers: Int?, val plays: Int?, val collectors: Int?, val comments: Int?, val lists: Int?, val votes: Int?, @Json(name = "collected_episodes") val collectedEpisodes: Int? )</ID>
    <ID>LongParameterList:User.kt$User$( val username: String?, @Json(name = "private") val isPrivate: Boolean?, val name: String?, val vip: Boolean?, @Json(name = "vip_ep") val vipEp: Boolean?, val ids: UserIds?, @Json(name = "joined_at") val joinedAt: ZonedDateTime?, val location: String?, val about: String?, val gender: String?, val age: Int = 0, val images: Images? )</ID>
  </CurrentIssues>
</SmellBaseline>
